杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 我想展示如何将主题组合在一起
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: I wanna show how
you can compose themes together and
在一个网站上使用多个主题
use multiple themes on a site to get
不需要大量的工作，就能获得巨大的效用。
a huge amount of utility
without a huge amount of work.
我在裸体课程中设计了一个主题,
So there's a theme that I built
as part of a naked course,
这叫做盖茨比主题活动
it's called Gatsby theme events and
it allows you to supply
一个 yml 文件充满了事件，并显示在您的网站上。
a yml file full of events and
display that on your site.
所以我希望能够得到这些事件，我们已经在内容事件,
So I wanna be able to get these events
that we've got in content events,
data.yml.
我希望这些可以在网站上以列表的形式提供。
I want those to be available
on the site as a list.
为了做到这一点，我们要去纱线工作区
So to do that,
we're going to yarn workspace negronies
加上 jlengstorf / gatsby-theme-events。
add jlengstorf/gatsby-theme-events.
所以我们将安装，然后在我们的 gastby-config,
So we'll get that installed and
then in our gastby-config,
我们需要安装这个主题或配置它。
we need to install that theme or
configure it.
所以我们要解决这些令人不安的事件。
So we're going to resolve
jlengstorf/gatsby-theme-events.
然后在选项中，我们想要改变基本路径。
And then in the options,
we wanna change the basePath.
所以这个的基本路径是事件。
So the basePath for
this is gonna be events.
然后我们需要知识路径
And then we want the contentPath
进入我们在这里定义的事件文件夹。
to go into that events folder
that we defined up here.
所以我们希望它能找到内容事件。
So we want it to find content events.
配置完成后,
Once this is configured,
我们想做和博士主题一样的事。
we kinda wanna do the same thing
that we did with the docs theme.
所以我们要影子的布局，所以 jlengstoref 和
So we're going to shadow the layout,
so jlengstoref and
注意，包上的名称空间可能使它看起来像
note that the namespace on that
package might make it seem like
隐藏会很奇怪，因为它会创建额外的文件夹,
shadowing would be weird because
it creates extra folders,
但它的工作原理完全一样，只是一个额外的文件夹。
but it works exactly the same
is just an extra folder.
所以我们要去参加一个活动 / 盖茨比主题的聚会
So we're gonna go
jlengstorf/gatsby-theme-events/components-
/ layout.js.
/layout.js.
然后在这里，我要导入布局从,
And then in it,
I'm gonna import layout from,
我们有三层，还有一层，组件，得到那个布局。
we've got three layers, one more,
to components, get that layout.
这就是我做错的地方，让人困惑。
That's what I did wrong, that's confusing.
然后我们要导出默认布局，好吗？
Then we're going to export default layout,
okay?
然后我们只需要链接到它。
And then we just need to link to it.
让我们回到这个索引页面。
So let's go back to this index page.
让我们再创建一个按钮
And let's create one more button and
it'll be to
事件页面，我们只说即将发生的事件。
the events page and
we'll just say Upcoming events.
杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 纱线工作区
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Yarn
workspace negronies
发展杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 和
develop
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: And
我们开始吧。
let's get this started.
杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 好的，我们开始运行了。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Okay,
we're up and running.
所以当我们回到我们的主页，刷新和
And so when we go back to our home page,
refresh and
我们可以看到，我们已经得到了我们即将举行的活动。
we can see that we've
got our upcoming events.
当我们点击浏览时，我们得到了一个即将发生的事件的列表
And when we click through we've
got a list of our upcoming events
列在我们创建的布局中。
listed in the layout that we've created.
这看起来不错，看起来像是在做我们想做的事情
So this is, it looks nice,
it looks like it's doing what we want and
花了我们两个文件，对吧？
it took us two files, right?
这就是我们现在所做的事情的力量。
So, and this is kind of the the power
of what we're doing here.
我们安装了两个主题，我的意思是，几乎没有什么代码发生。
We have two themes installed, and almost,
I mean, very little code happening.
我们基本上定义了自己的布局。
We've basically defined our own layout.
和一个主题用户界面，然后我们只是把布局放到几个不同的地方。
And a theme UI, and then we just drop that
layout into a couple different places.
我们已经能够用它建立一个完整的网站。
And we've been able to build
an entire site out of it.
所以能够遵循这个模式和
So it's very nice being able
to follow this pattern and
能够使用这个建立网站，因为它只是真正加速发展,
to be able to use this to build sites cuz
it just really accelerates development,
加速了我们快速启动新功能的能力。
accelerates our ability to quickly
throw a new functionality.
再说一次，如果你在一家代理机构工作，或者你在一家公司工作
And again, if you work at an agency or
something, or you're working in a company
有很多团队正在建立类似的登陆页面,
that has lots of teams that are building
similar kind of landing pages,
你会发现很多你重复做的事情
you'll just start to find that a lot
of the things that you do over and
可以再次打包成这些主题。
over again can be packaged
up into these themes.
然后以这样一种方式推出，你可以堆叠新的网站
And then pushed out in such a way
that you can stack together new sites
像乐高积木而不是必须建立，我已经建立了一个主页英雄框
like Legos instead of having to build,
I've already built a homepage hero box
一千次，我希望我不必再那样做了。
a thousand times,
I wish I didn't have to do that again.
安装主题，看到英雄主题，然后就完成了。
Install the theme,
saw the hero theme and be done with it.